If you're bored, make me some tea.
I can't believe you want
hot tea on a day like this.
It seems there are signs of
a strange cult in the castle city lately.
I hear they worship a god called Simila.
Right now, they're a minor nuisance at most.
I have to meet Legis today, so I'll be
returning to Tuldarr for some time.
What's wrong?
There's poison in this.
What?!
Oh, please don't worry.
Potions have no effect on me.
The magical power in my body immediately
breaks down their composition.
That's a relief.
Wait, no, it's not!
This pitcher was put here
for Lady Tinasha specifically.
Investigate it at once.
And even in Tuldarr,
have a defensive barrier up at all times.
Understood.
~ Unanswered Prayer ~
The water was filled by a lady-in-waiting
who's served the palace for five years.
Where did she acquire the poison?
A mysterious mage handed it
to her at the town market.
He told her that Lady Tinasha was really
a witch trying to deceive His Majesty...
Oh, Mila.
What do you want?
Lady Tinasha says
she won't be returning tonight.
It's top secret, but Legis
was attacked and is currently comatose.
Two of Tuldarr's successors to the throne,
attacked on the same day?
He's in Lady Tinasha's care,
so it's not life-threatening,
but she'll be staying in Tuldarr
for the time being.
Do you think both cases
share the same culprit?
If so, then they work unusually fast.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, Your Majesty.
Delilah
My name is Delilah.
When I heard about the witch's curse
placed on Your Majesty,
I couldn't stop myself
from making the journey here.
Please let me serve you.
I have the power to withstand the curse.
Where did you learn of it?
This is a confidential matter.
I come from a family of fortune tellers.
Our predictions are never wrong.
Fine by me.
We'll prepare a room for you.
Live here how you please.
Please wait a moment!
What about Lady Tinasha?
That's enough out of you.
This is my decision.
Do any of you object?
We received word from Tuldarr that
they've arrested Prince Legis's attacker.
Her spirit came to tell me directly as well.
But it seems there's no connection
to the mage who tried to poison Lady Tinasha.
Sounds like it.
What's with the gloomy look?
Cut it out.
Your Majesty.
With all due respect, I don't approve
of that woman being at your side.
Don't tell me you're trying
to provoke Lady Tinasha!
I wouldn't do that and risk
having her destroy the castle.
That's too eccentric, even for me.
Anyway, just leave it be.
I hear Legis's treatment will take some time.
Tinasha, you're back?
Long time no see.
How's Legis doing?
Fortunately, he's recovered.
Your Majesty!
I've called over a tailor.
If you'd like, please join me...
I haven't seen you around here before.
Are you a mage of some kind?
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Tinasha, and I come from Tuldarr.
Well, well.
So you're the princess of Tuldarr?
You seem to be quite close with that woman.
You should choose your friends more wisely.
What are you implying?
Befriending Tuldarr royalty
must come with lots of benefits, indeed.
I would never...
Um, you seem to be offering advice
without even introducing yourself.
And who exactly might you be?
I won't tolerate anyone
who insults a friend of mine.
How about you look in the mirror
before giving other people advice?
Go easy on the intimidation.
She's my lover.
I see...
So that insolent woman is his mistress.
Well, you know about His Majesty.
She claims she can withstand it.
By "it", you mean...
That's impossible for her.
She's sure to die.
What? Y-You mean it? I'll let His Majesty...
They both gave their consent, right?
I feel like...
I've been a fool this whole time.
Oscar, you idiot!
After saying you'd make sure I was happy...
I like the look on your face.
Travis.
What's it been, four hundred years?
Looks like you traveled through time,
thanks to my tips.
How'd it go with that man?
What?
You fell into a magic slumber to meet him,
and he shows no interest in you?
How sad.
Why don't you just kill her?
Humans aren't supposed to do that.
Humans are the only ones who ever do.
If you won't kill her, would you rather die?
Since you're suffering as is.
What?
Yes.
He's made me his mistress.
It looks like poison doesn't work
on Tuldarr's princess.
If you can, have her removed.
Can you get in the treasury?
I think I can, if I ask.
Be careful.
If you make it in, look for a box.
One containing a small orb
etched with a pattern.
You were quite the cautious one.
Y-Your Majesty! You have the wrong idea!
I'll receive a report later to see
who drove you to do this.
I already have someone
working to break my curse.
She may be odd, but she's a fine woman.
I've got my hands full with her.
Done already?
I shouldn't have gotten my hopes up.
As for the rest...
I'll have that man of yours pay instead.
I won't let you get close to him!
Take form!
Eh?
I don't want to die yet...
As for who Delilah was communicating with,
they're in a building in the Farsas castle city.
That shady cult, huh?
Head there at once and round them all up.
Don't let anyone slip away.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Your Majesty.
I just felt a powerful surge
of magic from the north.
It's on the level of a forbidden curse.
What?
Where's Tinasha?
Come help!
Lady Tinasha's going to die!
The hubby's here already?
Tinasha!
I wouldn't swing that sword so wantonly.
It's dangerous.
What did you do to her?
Nothing much.
We just had a little fun.
Don't think you can escape alive, monster.
You can tell I'm not human?
How amusing.
Her barrier, I see.
Enough of your mockery.
I'll burn you alive until nothing remains.
I won't let you kill him.
Tinasha!
I won't let you lay a finger on him,
no matter the cost.
What a fool you are.
All that, for someone
who shows no interest in you.
How pointless.
I'm tired.
I'll play with you some other day.
We arrested all the leaders of the cult
that sent Delilah to the castle.
But you didn't find the mage
who gave that servant the poison?
To summarize what we know,
they have two motives.
First, to seize a mysterious orb
they say is in the treasury.
Second, to assassinate Lady Tinasha,
or drive her away from this kingdom.
We'll have to sort through the treasury.
Something feels off...
Tinasha.
Um... I have a favor to ask.
Out with it.
Teach me how to use a sword.
Are your injuries healed?
Yes.
Well, rather than healed, I think
Travis regrew all the parts I'd lost.
Regrew it all?
What is that monster Travis, anyway?
He's one of the highest-ranking demons.
In common parlance, a demon king.
That aside, why did you tie up that woman?
Did you two have a lovers' spat?
What are you talking about?
I was leading her on from the beginning.
I had my suspicions the moment
she mentioned my curse.
It ended up being the same group
that tried to poison you.
You should have told me that from the start.
If I had known, I...
Wouldn't have shattered any windows?
I didn't shatter any this time!
That reminds me, when we fought
against Druza, I borrowed your vision.
Can anyone see like you do
with enough practice?
It's impossible unless you're born with it,
but you have the potential.
I do?
If you develop the awareness.
That can be something
I teach you some other time.
Thanks.
I will say though,
you have the fundamentals down.
Before I was crowned queen, I received
a short crash course in swordplay.
It's fairly traditional Farsas technique.
How can you tell?
That's absolutely right.
Must have been an odd fellow,
teaching a trueborn mage to use a sword.
He was a strict but kind man.
How did it go, Valt?
A failure on both ends.
They were captured.
Is that really okay?
It's fine.
Powerful as she may be, she's a lot easier
to handle than when she was a witch.
This has never happened before.
Here's a list of all
the articles in the treasury.
This is going to be a pain.
Once we've had trustworthy
people verify all the items,
we'll seal off the underground labyrinth.
There's a labyrinth under the castle?
Forty years ago,
a burglar got into the treasury.
They made an escape,
and no one found out what they took.
The king at the time, my grandfather,
was quite distraught.
So he built a labyrinth?
He built it so that once someone enters,
the doors can't be opened for a full day
by anyone outside the royal family.
Even royalty can't open it
from the inside for a full day.
I suppose it really does run in the family.
Did you say something?
So you take no issue to the labyrinth
being sealed off as planned?
Let me see...
Underground Labyrinth    Depths of the Farsas Treasury
I swear...
You really can be unreasonable at times.
Think of it as practice.
This path seems pretty straight
for a labyrinth, though.
I bet he just wanted to call it a labyrinth.
What's a lake doing under the castle?
What's more, I sense something ominous.
Could this be the Lake of Silence?
Lake of Silence
What exactly is the Lake of Silence?
It's from an old Farsas legend.
An inhuman creature is said to have
pulled Akashia from the lake.
The people drew close
and settled in its vicinity, or so it goes.
I was sure it was just myth.
I can't believe
they built a castle on top of it.
What's a door doing there?
Tinasha!
That idiot!
Th-Thank you...
Are you okay?
I think I broke some ribs.
Can you heal yourself?
Actually, it looks like I can't use magic.
What do you mean?
This lake water...
It must contain some
of the same material as Akashia.
Drinking it disturbs the magic in your body,
making you unable to cast spells.
This looks a little familiar.
What is this place?
Basically, this has got to be
Grandpa's hideout.
If it has fresh water,
I'd like to wash this water off.
Feeling better?
Yes, this should do.
That reminds me, why are you
going through the treasury all of a sudden?
Looking for something?
Oh, I guess I never told you about it.
That shady cult was after
something in this treasury.
We're not sure what exactly it is.
Apparently, it's a red orb
that fits in your palm.
What's wrong?
Don't touch that orb!
Eh?
Don't let anyone touch it.
No, don't look for it...
Don't leave me...
Tinasha!
You should tell me if you've got a fever!
Oscar.
The same orb exists in Tuldarr as well.
One of a different color.
Really?
I sealed away the one in Tuldarr
four hundred years ago.
Sealed it away?
Is it dangerous?
It holds an incredible power,
unprecedented in magical history.
That orb sends its user into the past,
a feat no mage or demon is capable of.
It does sound dangerous,
but can't it be useful when used right?
Not exactly.
When you use it, everything you have
is erased as you go back in time,
and you must rebuild it all
from the very beginning.
When I was a child,
there was someone who saved my life.
But the price he paid
was giving up everything he had,
from his past to his future.
So that was the man who saved your life?
I won't leave you.
I don't want to change the past.
I won't look for the orb
if you don't want me to,
and I'm okay with sealing it away.
So don't you ever cry like that again.
If this was my grandfather's hideout,
there should be a shortcut that
doesn't pass through the treasury.
"Don't leave me," huh?
This is it.
Tinasha, we can go back.
You already knew my name the moment we met.
Why must you come in through the window?
Are your broken bones healed?
Yes, I'm all better.
Sorry to worry you like that.
Actually, when I brought you back,
everyone was mad at me, even Als.
I-I'm sorry.
No, it was my fault.
So what do we do with that orb?
We can seal it away if you want.
Isn't it an heirloom from your mother?
An heirloom? My mother?
In that case, I'll ask my father.
Y-Yes.
Tinasha.
I don't know anything.
And I don't need to know.
Everything I've done is by my own choice.
I have no complaints or regrets.
The same holds true for every choice I make,
regardless of time or place.
So stop feeling sorry.
Oscar...
You figured it out.
I'm glad I came to this age and met you.
It's only been four months since I woke up,
but you've made me so happy.
This is enough for me.
In the future, even if we part ways,
you'll always be my...
Good night.
~ Unseen Visage ~